(Leonard:)It's also a problem
because we don't even know
(Leonard:)if the aliens
who find this can see.
(Leonard:)I mean, they might
communicate
(Leonard:)in a totally
different way than us.
(Raj:)Like when my dog is mad at me,
(Raj:)she tells me
by peeing in my slippers.
(Leonard:)That's actually a valid example.
(Leonard:)Animals do deliver messages
through scent.
(Raj:)Bees talk to each other
by dancing.
(Raj:)Whales have their songs.
Penny has about 20 different
ways of rolling her eyes
(Leonard:)that each mean
something different.
(Raj:)Okay, so, what it
sounds like is,
(Raj:)what we want is a device
(Raj:)that can deliver a message
through not only sight,
(Raj:)but other senses, as well.
(Leonard:)The most basic sense that any
space-faring civilization
(Leonard:)would have to possess is touch.
Ooh. Ooh, ooh!
(Raj:)We could make
a video-playing device
(Raj:)that simultaneously translates
the information
(Raj:)into a tactile medium.
(Leonard:)All we have to do is rig up
a 3-D communication system!
We-we can totally do that!
I know!
This is great!
(Leonard:)Yeah, you know what else it is?
What?
(Howard:)Exactly what Sheldon
and Howard said.
(Raj:)Well, thank you
for peeing in my slippers.